It's cute.
かわいいですね
The dimples are so cute.
エクボがめちゃくちゃかわいい
Even when I laughed.
笑ったときも
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you told?
言われる?
often.
よく
It's said sometimes.
たまに言われます
Dimples are a pitfall of love.
エクボは恋の落とし穴だね
I agree.
そうですね
Can I ask you to call me cute?
かわいらしく言ってもらっていいですか?
Dimples are a pitfall of love.
エクボは恋の落とし穴
cute?
かわいい?
amazing.
すごい
That's what he said.
言ってた
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいですね
It tastes sweet.
甘い味がするね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It gives a really rich center.
すごい濃厚な 中央 してくれるんだね
Are you nervous?
緊 張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
cute.
かわいい
Is it a long time?
久々ですか?
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It is the door to the future.
未来への扉です
Feel like opening it?
開けたくなった?
I wanted to open it.
開けたくなった
It's hope for me.
俺にとって希望なんで
I'm among the super cute people.
超かわいい人に入ってる
So cute.
すげーかわいい
Well, why are you hiding it?
あれ、なんで隠すの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
To a cute person.
かわいい人に
Can I join the fans?
ファンの人に入れるの?
This is a bad place to look.
見ちゃダメなところです
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Don't look at it.
見ちゃダメ
Look at me.
見てて
That's something I don't really understand.
あんまわかんないところね
amazing.
すごい
The style is really nice.
ス タ イ ルめっちゃいいね
That's really nice, Style.
めちゃくちゃいいね、スタイ
Le.
ル
Amazing style.
すごい スタイル
cute.
かわいい
Were you wearing a swimsuit?
水着になったりしてた?
Just a little bit.
ちょこっとだけ
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Well, there's still plenty of time.
じゃあ、まだ余裕だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですよ
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
behind.
後ろ
Little by little.
ちょこちょこ
I touched your butt.
お尻に触った
You look so erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロい格好してるね
This kind of pose.
こういうポーズは
Don't feel like a friend.
仲間感しないで
This is a gravure idol.
これはグラビアアイドルだもんね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
But it's super cute.
でも、超かわいい
That's amazing.
すげえいいね
Your butt is beautiful.
お尻きれいだな
There's a stain.
シミができてるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Have you ever worn a thong?
Tバックとか履いたことある?
No, thong.
ないです、Tバック
do not have?
ない?
It's getting really messy though.
すっごいブシャブシャになってるけど
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
Is it easy for me to paint?
私、塗りやすいか
too.
も
You look like a half-Japanese.
ハ ーフみたいな顔してるね
Isn't that often said?
よく言われないですか?
It's said sometimes.
たまに言われます
That's what you say.
言われますよね
When?
いつの間に?
Was it taken?
取られてたの?
can be?
あり?
why?
なんで?
Why?
どうして?
It's delicious.
うまいね
Umai?
う ま い?
Was it good to go straight?
スッと行くのがうまかったですか?
professional?
プロ?
Looks like a pro.
プ ロ みたい
Are you a professional?
プロなの?
I'm sure this is when I was watching it.
確かに、これ見なぎの時にね
You may be forced to remove it by the photographer.
カメラマンに無理やり剥がされることあるかもしれない
Flicker flicker.
チラチラチラチラ
I can see it.
見えてるよ
A sneak peek?
チラ?
Did you give me a glimpse?
チラしてくれたの?
You're so kind.
優しいね
Did you give me a glimpse?
チラしてくれたの?
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だね
Super soft.
超柔らかい
Is it more open?
もっと開いてるか
Wow, it's delicious.
すげえ、おいしい
delicious.
おいしい
It tastes like banana.
バナナの味がする
Banana flavor.
バナナの味
Because I'm eating a lot of bananas.
バナナいっぱい食べてるから
amazing.
すごい
cute.
かわいい
It's really cute though.
めちゃめちゃかわいいんだけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hey, show me your side.
ちょっと さ、脇見せて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's beautiful.
綺麗じゃん
It's smooth.
ツルツルだね
Chulchuru.
チュルチュル
delicious.
おいしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a beautiful body.
綺麗な体だね
Hey, show me your legs.
ちょっとさ、脚見せて
That's naughty.
やらしい
Look good
格好して
Ru.
る
This is such a naughty look!
これ がやらしい格好ってなおか
hey.
ね
Look, it's getting stained.
ちょっと ほら、しみになってる
difficult.
難しい
Is it difficult?
難しいですか?
difficult.
難しい
He's a pervert.
変態さんだ
By now?
今頃?
He's a pervert.
変態さんだ
Did you notice it just now?
今頃気づいた?
beautiful.
綺麗
around here
この 辺
has fallen into the middle.
は 中んぼになっちゃったね
It's pink.
ピンク色だ
It's starting to grow.
生えかけてるね
that's right.
そうです
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Did you shave?
剃ってたの?
Did you shave and go in?
剃って入っちゃったの?
I went in.
入っちゃいました
It's really beautiful, though.
すごい綺麗だよ、でも
You've never looked good, have you?
格 好したことないでしょ?
No.
ないです
He opened it with his own hands and ate it.
自分の手でさ、開いてから食ったのって
Leave it like this?
このまま?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Wow, it's delicious.
すげえ、おいしいよ
That's naughty.
やらしい
It's really narrow.
すっごい狭いな
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
Very low.
すっごい低い
It's amazing it's coming.
すげえ来てる
Sorry.
ごめんね
short.
短い
I don't know myself.
自分でわかんない
Looks like it's going to break.
折れそうだな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいってこと?
yes.
はい
Offered.
申し出される
But I'm being pushed out.
押し出されるんだけど
Are you pushing it out?
押し出してるでしょ?
I haven't pushed it out.
押し出してない
Soaked.
びしょびしょに
I was surprised.
びっくりした
what happened?
どうしたの?
amazing.
すごい
I fell asleep.
寝ちゃったね
寝ちゃった
I fell asleep again.
もう一回寝ちゃったね
Soaked.
びしょびしょ
So cute.
すげえ可愛い
cute.
可愛い
It's so cute.
すげえ可愛いね
I like it.
好きです
Seriously?
マジで?
Isn't the way you touch it so erotic?
触り方めっちゃエロくない?
amazing.
すごい
Looks like it's about to come out.
出ちゃいそう
terrible.
やばい
It's already out.
もう出ちゃった
It feels a little too good.
ちょっと気持ちよすぎて
It hit my face.
顔かかったね
Wasn't it amazing?
すごくなかった?
Momentum.
勢いが
I fell asleep again.
もう 一回寝ちゃったね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Shall I wipe it off a bit?
ちょっと拭こうか
sorry.
ごめんなさい
I laughed.
笑ってきました
Why did you say that?
何で言っちゃったんですか?
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎて
It's too early.
早すぎます
Sorry.
ごめんね
It got on my face.
顔にかかっちゃったね
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎて
That's no good, right?
ダメでしょ
It's delicious.
うまいね
The producer told me about it.
プロデューサーさんに教えてもらった
You like dicks.
ちんちん好きだね
I like it.
好きです
It's narrow, that's for sure.
狭いね、確かに
Can I smile again?
もう一回笑っていいですか?
You have a beautiful face.
きれいな顔あるね
I'm full on my stomach.
うつむっぱいな
Awesome.
すげー
It's tough.
きついね
How does it work?
どうやって動いてるんですか?
It hurts so bad.
すっげー痛い
I'm laughing right away.
すぐ笑ってる
tight.
きつい
It's really tough.
めちゃくちゃきついね
My throat is tight.
喉がきついな
It's closed.
閉めてる
My nose is very weak.
鼻がめっちゃ弱い
It's getting hard.
固くなってる
mouth?
口?
mouth.
口
It's no good.
ダメなんだ
Is there something wrong with your nose?
鼻がダメなの?
Why?
どうして?
I was planning on releasing it.
出す予定だったんだけど
My lower eyes started to get cloudy.
下目くもりだしちゃった
amazing.
すごい